♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
(KNOCKING)
But what could…
Hey, you!
What are you doing here?
No one’s allowed in the dormitory
without my authorization!
How’d you get in here?
Uh…well, I…
Hey!
Plain, but not bad.
But I wonder who gave it to me.
And why.
Why?
I might have an idea.
You know what day it is today?
Uh…Tuesday!
Yes, but not just any Tuesday!
It’s Saint Valentine’s Day!
The day all lovers celebrate!
Lovers?
Yes. And I can guess
exactly which boy
might want to give you
a present, can’t you?
Hey, there’s Aelita!
Thanks, Jeremie!
You know, the first time
I see someone in the morning,
I tend to say, “good morning,”
but then again, maybe I’m
a little old-fashioned.
For the necklace. Thank you.
The um…necklace?
Your Valentine’s Day present!
It’s lovely.
Uh…yeah, um…
Well, you’re welcome!
It’s only natural! (CHUCKLES)
Well, see you in history class!
See you, Aelita!
You didn’t give it to her, did you.
Was it that obvious?
Yeah. But lucky for you,
love has made Aelita blind.
Oh, come on, Ulrich.
Most historians believe
that Valentine’s Day
is associated with
the Roman Lupercalia…
Hey, Ulrich, it wouldn’t be you
who gave her that necklace
by any chance?
You out of your mind or something?
I didn’t even know it was Valentine’s Day.
…marked the first day
of the Roman spring.
An important day in ancient Rome.
Jeremie, what rhymes with, uh, tulip?
I don’t know. Microchip?
Paperclip? Hypocrite?
Okay, nevermind.
What are you writing?
Nothing!
A poem?
No.
Is it for Yumi?
No!
It’s…biology homework.
Biology homework that rhymes, huh?
That’s interesting.
Odd, the necklace. It wasn’t you, was it?
Do I have to remind you that Aelita
is supposed to be my cousin?
Yes, except that we both
know she isn’t your cousin.
Yeah? What is it was me?
Aelita isn’t your property as far as I know.
Aha! You see! You admit it!
I didn’t admit anything.
You just said it was you!
Hey, have you gone bananas?
Your eyesight’s not great,
but your hearing’s worse!
I--
(CLEARS THROAT)
If you have more important subjects
to discuss than today’s lesson,
I suggest you do so
in the principal’s office!
In your case, Odd,
this comes as no surprise.
But you, Jeremie, a
model student in all areas,
I simply don’t understand.
Well, I…
Two hours of detention should help you
to find some more convincing arguments.
And you’re lucky it’s Valentine’s Day
or I’d have given you at least four.
I’m still waiting for an answer.
Hey, why don’t we call a truce, okay?
Was it you who gave her the necklace?
Yes or no?
Okay, then. No truce.
Come on, Einstein. It’s stupid to
fight over such a little thing.
He’s right.
What’s more, Odd has every right
to give Aelita a present if he wants to.
Uh, Ulrich?
Could I talk to you for a second?
(SIGHS) Well, only if
it’s really important.
For me?
Is this for Valentine’s Day?
(LAUGHS) No, it’s for Christmas!
Of course it’s for Valentine’s Day!
What do you think, hm?
Come on! Open it, stupid!
Wow!
A ticket to the Subsonics concert!
Isn’t that your favorite group?
Well, yeah.
I must be dreaming.
Yumi, I’ve got something for you.
Oh! Thank you, William!
I must be dreaming.
Sissi, I wrote you a little poem.
“To tell you how much I flip
“If not with a tulip
“How I’m a victim of your charms
“And long to hold you in my arms
“With you, I never feel gloomy,
My little, uh…Sissi.”
Oh, Ulrich! It rhymes!
It’s so beautiful!
William!
Your bouquet is beautiful!
How did you know
that I liked roses!
I didn’t.
But I figured you were
like all the other girls.
How romantic, William! (LAUGHS)
Just a bit awkward!
Thank you, William.
You couldn’t have made me happier.
(UNNERVING MUSIC)
Look, it’s ridiculous to fight
over such a puny little thing.
William had every right to give Yumi a present
and so did Sissi with Ulrich, right?
Hey, I don’t think you’re the
one to talk right now, okay?
By the way, does anyone
know where Aelita is?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Settle down and take your seats.
(STUDENTS CHATTER)
Please open your textbooks to page 27.
The anatomical structure of muscles.
Where were you?
I looked for you everywhere.
I was…um, uh…
(PULSING)
Do you think that we could
go to sector five after class?
I know where to find the data
for making the antivirus!
The one that'll free you from XANA?
You mean to say it…
it just came to you just like that?
Let’s just say that your necklace inspired me.
The problem is that given
everybody’s bad mood today,
I doubt that Odd or Ulrich or Yumi
are gonna want to go with you.
I can go by myself!
No, it’s too dangerous.
Don’t forget, XANA’s
ready to go to any extreme
to steal your memory, Aelita.
Please, Jeremie.
I'm positive I'm on the right track.
And with an Overboard, I’m sure
I can get away from the monsters.
Even the latest ones
like the scyphozoa.
Please?
Gah! Ha--Ho! (YELLS)
Oh! Why, Jeremie!
(LAUGHTER)
That’s two more hours.
That’s four hours of detention.
I’m going to have to suspend you
if you do anything else!
Jim sees Spider Man stuck to the ceiling,
my best pupil is acting like a clown…
Valentine’s Day is making everyone crazy!
Yumi says she’ll go with me to Lyoko!
After everything that’s happened today,
it’ll be nice to get something accomplished.
(UNNERVING MUSIC)
Ready, ladies?
I am starting up the process.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Aelita.
Scanner Yumi.
Scanner Aelita.
Virtualization.
Hey. That’s weird.
(PULSING)
Vehicles for the ladies
coming right up.
Materialization.
You need to go due east
to get to the edge of the sector.
No way. I’m heading north.
But…I don’t understand.
You’re supposed to go to sector five!
Sorry, Yumi.
Yumi?
Aelita, what’s going on!
Yumi, can you hear me?
Are you okay?
I’d be lying if I said I was.
What’s gotten into her?
I don’t know! She’s lost it!
You’ve absolutely got to stop her.
She’s headed due north.
Okay. I’ll try.
But I’m gonna need some backup.
I’m on it.
Jeremie, we’re supposed to be
doing two hours of detention now!
Speak slower! I can’t understand a word!
An attack by XANA.
Is that all you can think of
as an excuse for us to make up?
Odd, listen to me. It’s an emergency.
Just get over here now!
No cell phones in detention!
Where is Jeremie Belpois?
Odd! Odd? Can you hear me?
Relax, Ulrich.
Surprise!
The latest Subsonics CD! Look!
Not bad for getting in the mood
before going to the concert!
Uh, Sissi…uh, l-listen.
You’re right.
Let’s not talk!
(WHISPERS) Let’s listen.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hello? Yeah. Yeah. Jeremie.
Okay. I’ll be right there.
Hm?
Right. I’ll take care of it.
Hey! Where are you going!
Jeremie just reminded me
of a really important
thing I have to do.
What?
Uh, well, leave.
Okay, Jeremie. I see her.
Yumi, do you know how
Aelita got that necklace?
I think she found it on her doorstep.
Do you think XANA could’ve put it there?
I’m launching a superscan.
We’ll know in a minute.
In my opinion, it’s that dumb necklace
that gives XANA control over Aelita.
He wants to lead her
straight to the scyphozoa.
Oh, no. That’s exactly
what I was afraid of.
Looks like XANA’s activated a tower.
Don’t panic, Jeremie.
I’ve just about caught up to her.
And I was about to say this was too easy.
Jeremie, I don’t want to sound pessimistic,
but if Ulrich and Odd could hurry up a bit!
You see, Jim, Aelita’s got 104 fever,
so naturally she wants to see her cousin.
He’s her only family here!
A minute ago, it was 103!
Right! Her temperature
keeps going up by the minute!
(CHUCKLES)
What do you take me for?
Some kind of idiot?
Well, um…no! No, Jim.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Excuse me.
Yeah. Well, no. Jim doesn’t believe me.
About Aelita’s fever.
Okay. Put him on, Ulrich.
Here you are, Jim.
It’s…it's for you.
Yes?!
Yes? Uh, of course!
I-I understand, Mister Delmas!
Huh?
Do you hear me, Jim?
Let Della Robbia see
his cousin!
Very well! Whatever you say, sir!
Say, uh, when you have time,
could I speak to you
about a personal matter?
It’s about Suzanne Hertz.
I…well, uh…it’s a tunnel!
We’re about to get cut off!
How did you manage that with the principal?
I wrote a new program.
Stern, Della Robbia,
Hurry up! Things
are getting hot here!
Jeremie, tell me you’ve
reprogrammed a new vehicle!
Don’t worry!
Give me 10 seconds.
Yeah! Nice going, Yumi!
Do you still have a visual on Aelita?
She took off for sector one. The ice sector.
Use the way tower!
On the Overboard?
Are you absolutely sure about that?
Uh, well, yes.
There’s no reason you couldn’t.
If you’re wrong, I swear I’ll…
(YELLS)
You swear you’ll what?
Um, nothing.
Can’t do without me, huh?
You won’t get mad
if I save Aelita, will you?
Odd.
No, let him, Ulrich. He’s right.
I was being stupid.
I don’t blame you, Jeremie. I understand.
I’m a pretty charming guy.
It’s only natural you’d be jealous of me.
(CHUCKLES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Aelita, you must stop obeying XANA!
Leave me alone!
No!
Jeremie, could you just
remind me what’ll happen
if I fall into the digital sea?
If I were you, I’d avoid it.
Well then if you could help me
out of here, I’d appreciate it!
I’m bringing you back.
But it’s gonna take a couple minutes!
I was afraid you were gonna say that.
(YELLS)
Happy to see me?
I sure am.
Move it, Jeremie.
I can’t hold her for long.
I’m doing all I can!
Say, Yumi, what did you
think of my poem for Sissi?
Ulrich, this is really not the time.
Because, in fact,
I actually wrote it for you.
I can’t hold on!
Yumi!
(YELLS)
Remind me to boost that program.
Ulrich, Odd’s about to need your help.
Aelita!
It’s me! Odd!
No!
(SCREECHING)
Aelita!
Ulrich, hurry up.
I’m almost there.
You okay, Odd?
Brillian. As usual.
That bad, huh?
Laser arrow!
Aelita! Stop!
Hey, that’s cheating!
Jeremie, we’re never gonna make it.
You’ve got to think of something.
I do have one idea, but it’s awfully risky.
Odd, aim for Aelita.
Huh? Are you crazy!
Hey, don’t forget that if
Aelita loses all her life points,
she’ll disappear forever!
XANA wants her memory.
He won’t risk losing that.
Deep down, he wants her alive
as much as we do.
Are you sure?
No. But I can’t think of anything else.
Okay. Here I go.
(BEEPS)
Only 30 life points left!
Well, you want me to stop?
No!
I just hope I’m right.
(GROANS)
XANA’s givin’ up!
Yes!
Uh-oh. The scyphozoa’s at it again.
It was too good to be true.
Only 10 life points left!
It’s okay!
What’s going on?
Why are you aiming at me?
Tower deactivated.
I’m gonna study this.
You never know.
I might be able to get
some interesting
information about XANA.
Anyway, Aelita, from now on,
you don’t take any presents from anyone.
Promise.
You know, Jeremie saved my life,
And that’s the nicest Valentine’s
present anyone can hope for.
Yeah, but that sure won’t save him
from being suspended
for missing four hours of detention.
The principal’s not gonna be
too happy about that!
But I’m sure there’s a solution!
Hey, what are you looking at me for?
I’m really happy to be going
to the concert with you,
but you won’t forget to talk to
your father beforehand, huh?
Don’t worry. I’ll get Jeremie out of this.
Now that’s a real friend.
Ready to sacrifice himself for his pal.
Are you sure he’s sacrificing himself
as much as all that?
He doesn’t seem to be bothered by it.
Maybe not.
But it was for me that he wrote the poem.
Poor Sissi!
(LAUGHTER)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO